Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
I remember very little from when
I still went to school.
but there's one day I'll never forget:
My first natural history class.
The teacher was trying to explain
what a natural constant is.
Something that. whatever happens.
will never change.
He gave all kinds of examples
of natural constants:
The passage of time. the tides.
the expansion of the universe.
birth. death. gravity.
the contradiction of human nature.
the change from day to night.
and night to day.
photosynthesis in plants
and many more.
Very excited with all these new terms.
I got home at night. eager
to tell my father.
but of course. my dad wasn't impressed.
My dad has always been very smart.
I think he's the
smartest person I've ever met.
He just answered that. for him.
there were only two true constants:
Family and change.
I didn't understand
what he meant that night.
what he meant for a long time
How long?
17 seconds.
I won! I beat you.
- Your turn.
- No. it's freezing!
I'm the king of the lagoon.
Oliver. no.
Come on. jump in.
No. I'm scared.
But there's nothing Benja. don't worry.
Trust me. get in.
I'm just scared. it looks too deep.
What are you going to name that frog?
Um. "Manchitas"
Because of the spots on her back.
No! Name her Kermit. like Kermit the Frog.
Is Pink going to be jealous?
I don't think so.
She's been feeling very lonely.
Who is Kermit the Frog?
Salvador.
Chava
Don't call me that!
What do you want?
Bring Guillermina.
What took you so long?
Uh. Asshole!
What happened to your face?
Camouflage.
It's big.
Also far.
Not for Guille.
Go. watch out.
Hello little dog.
Come little dog.
Come.
Doggy. come here.
That's it!
Are the monster's teeth like these?
Hey! Don't touch that!
No. they are much worse.
Those are not teeth. those are fangs.
they can kill you with one bite.
What's that?
It’s my pet.
- Another one?
- It's ours.
You didn't find more?
- It's called "Manchitas".
- No. it's called Kermit.
Can we make a little house for it?
No problem.
I'll take care of it.
Did you come down yesterday?
No.
Two days without noise.
Are you hungry?
Yes. A little.
Go with Benjamin.
I'll let you know in a while.
Smells good. what is it?
Protein.
What did you put in it?
The...
The frog?
Manchitas?
You promised
to take care of her!
Benny. understand we have to eat.
She was mine!
When my parents come home
I'll tell them you killed my frog!
Please. sit down and eat!
I don't want anything!
I don't want to eat!
You are the worst brother in the world!
You are poop!
Poop! You hear me?
Poop!
I said sit down!
We eat what we have. dumb head!
That frog is better on your plate
than in that damn jar over there!
But if you don't want it. I will eat it.
I won't eat it!
Why don't you get like this
when we kill the dogs?
That has nothing to do with this!
The dogs are for him!
Manchitas was mine!
She was mine!
It was so Pink
wouldn't feel so lonely!
Did you finish with the dishes?
Yes.
Benjamin cries about everything.
I have a crybaby and a coward.
I'm screwed.
Come on. he is seven.
Give him a break. he misses mom and dad.
Well. I also miss many things.
but here I am busting my ass. you see?
Benjamin! Go with him right now!
Let's go upstairs!
Quickly Benjamin!
Get down!
Run!
Everything will be alright.
We'll take care of it!
Don't come out. okay?
Why the fuck don't you knock?
One of the hanged fell.
One. two. three.
Benja. how’s that knot going?
Help him tie that knot. Run!
One. two. three.
Can't you tie a fucking knot?
Of course we can. Look!
PÁRVULOS
Still not growing. Shit!
I told you this was my lucky stick.
I'll hit the monster
if he breaks free.
Benja. your stick is useless
against the monster.
If he sees you
he will swallow you in one bite.
What if I put it in his mouth?
It breaks in a second.
Rake. please!
What if I stuck it in his eye?
It will just get angrier.
Rake!
His senses are more developed than ours.
Rake. damn it!
Can't you hear me?
Cut out the weeds.
get water from the pond.
also compost.
Hey! What's wrong with you?
It was about to end.
Aren’t you sick of watching
the same damn movie?
We need to set more bird traps.
We haven't caught anything in weeks.
Well. then we need to use more
plant fertilizer.
We do that. And meanwhile?
You can't keep risking him like this.
It's dangerous for him.
It's dangerous for both of us.
Then don't go!
I don't want to expose him.
but I can't go alone nor stay alone.
One of us has to stay here
and take food to the basement.
Should we leave him or what?
Salvador
I can't sleep.
I'm scared.
“At first. the father was utterly opposed
to the idea of leaving his children
at the mercy of the forest”.
“How can you even say that. woman?”
“What kind of father do you think I am?
He replied angrily.”
“The woman. who was keen to get
rid of the burden of the children.
did not rest until she convinced
the weak lumberjack
that this was
the only thing they could do”.
“The children were not really asleep.
so they heard the whole conversation
by their door”.
“The next morning.
the children followed their father
deep into the forest”.
“Hansel trailed behind.
dropping breadcrumbs
to mark the path that would
take them back home”.
- “We have to go to the forest”...
- I think he’s asleep.
Do you think the monster ate our parents?
No. Benjamin. how can you say that?
Then. why haven't they come back?
Have they forgotten we're here?
What if they caught the virus and
don't have the vaccine?
No. of course not.
That's from the old world.
You've better go to sleep
we're leaving early in the morning.
Benjamin! What the hell are you doing?
Are you a fucking idiot or what?
You know you can’t go in
the basement!
Do you want to die?
When will you let me see it?
Not until you’re 10!
Oliver saw it before he was 10!
If you get distracted
it will kill you in one bite.
don't you get it?
We have to work together. Benja.
No room for kids here.
I'm bigger but you have two legs.
we're equal.
We have to find some food.
Grab your stuff.
Let's go.
Please. don't go!
The pandemic came this far?
It reached the entire world.
but that wasn't the problem.
Let's go.
Don't go too far away.
Look what I found!
No. no. no. don't come up here!
There's nothing to see here.
What if we moved to the abandoned house?
So each of us could have his own room.
What about the monster?
Why do you care so much for it?
We can't let it starve to death.
We are not like that.
After all. it's like an animal.
like your frog. also like Pink.
We found it and now
we have to take care of it.
Besides.
if mom and dad come back
and don't see us.
they'll think something happened to us.
Chava. do you miss it?
Miss what?
Well. everything. as it was before.
Sometimes. when I get bored.
And when you're not?
What about you?
Do you miss anything?
Mmm. Dad used to snore very loudly.
Like this. look!
That would wake me up.
I also miss mom's pancakes
with apple and pecans.
Pancake Saturdays.
They'll surely be back
for Christmas. right?
The trumpets passed through here.
It was just one body. but they
took out his hearth and everything.
When are you coming back?
We have to go around.
I can't go up the hill
with all this stuff.
Today it jumped at me!
It almost got me!
Benja asked why
we can't leave the house.
What did you say?
Well. nothing.
What am I going to say?
Well. the truth.
he understands more than you think.
You still have dog?
If it's over before we get back...
Well. yes. I know.
You don't have to remind me.
Good night. Oliver.
Good night.
Over and out.
Rest stop.
Does it hurt?
Only when I laugh.
I'm going to the river to fill the canteen.
It's loaded. okay?
Be careful.
Don't move from here.
No!
Let's go. let's go!
Where is the backpack?
Run! Grab your bike. let's go!
Salvador. Benny.
Pick up.
Pick up. dammit!
I don't want to be here alone.
Salvador. Benny? Pick up!
Just tell me you're okay!
Why didn't you answer?
Heat up water for a bath. run.
I lost the radio.
The backpack fell into the river.
I fucked up.
Let me go!
Help. help!
Let's go Benjamin!
Omega-virus. that's what they called it.
Many years ago. before you were born.
another virus stopped this world.
Not what you saw in mom and dad.
Something else.
The pandemic?
It was also very hard.
People could not go out
and live their lives.
The economy collapsed.
I don't know what that is
but that's what I've been told.
Humanity was in urgent
and desperate need for a vaccine.
They were vaccinated
with whatever they could find.
At first everything was going well.
but then
the virus kept mutating.
they kept updating the vaccines.
at some point. the virus mutated
faster than the vaccines.
They had to administer a vaccine
that was not well tested. so...
the Omega
was one of the side effects.
It is believed that 83 percent of people
already have omega.
Will they die?
Benja!
You don't know how surprised
I am that they’re not dead already.
So. those screams at night are...
It's them.
Sometimes they fight
because dad wants to...
Eat?
No.
Ride.
I don't want them to die!
I want them to be cured!
So do we Benja.
but there is no cure.
Then why do you have them locked up?
I believe there is a cure.
it must exist or they will discover it.
We just have to be patient.
The world is fucked up.
Tell me who the hell
is going to discover it?
Mom and dad took care of us
when the omega started.
They took us out of the city.
We couldn't live there.
it was very dangerous.
We were wandering for a long time.
Then we found this house
and everything changed.
They taught us everything
we needed to survive.
Until...
No.
Well. something good is
going to come out of this.
Benja...
We don't have to hide
them from you anymore.
You are a big boy now.
You know the truth.
Now you will help us take care of them.
Calm down mom.
it’s just your sunglasses.
Ready? Let's go!
Hey. hey.
Give her a chance.
It's been ages since she came out.
Fresh air. mom! And some sun!
Hey! No biting!
Look mom. it’s the wilderness.
These are trees.
I tried to paint them when I was little.
but they came out all wrong.
The teacher told me
they were too thin and all crooked.
One day.
you and dad took me to see them.
I can still remember.
Look mom. touch them.
Benja. you have to understand.
Mom is not what she used to be.
She can't understand you.
I know she understands me.
Look mom.
Touch them. feel them.
Feel them. they are trees.
See. I told you.
Keep a tight grip.
I don't like this.
We need to go back.
Can’t leave dad alone for so long.
I know they can change.
They can remember who they were before.
Trust me. we're going to train them.
Let me train them for a few days.
You'll see I'm right.
Let's go Benja. is late.
I know it's been a hard day for you.
- I don't want to go!
- Benja let's go!
- No!
- Listen to me!
Benja. go to bed.
Benja. it's really late.
Tomorrow will be a long day.
Sit down.
Sit down!
Go away. go away!
I'm OK. I'm OK.
We're not going to chain them?
I don't think so.
They've earned it.
Benja. you were right.
They are improving.
I want to try something.
Look mom.
Say horse.
Horse.
Say it mom.
Look mom. it's a pig.
Say pig.
- Pig.
- Benja.
We have made progress.
but let’s keep it real.
They will never be like before.
What? You just said I was right.
Benja. understand.
we can train them a bit.
but you won't make them talk.
or remind them of who you are.
Anyway.
I think it's time for them to have dinner.
Oliver.
That's gross!
Why do they like to eat that?
I don't know if they like it. but
they eat it and that is enough.
"Pig"
She spoke!
Pig. Do you remember food. mom?
- Food.
- Ham. sausage.
Do you remember. mom?
Speaking of dinner. tomorrow is Christmas.
I know there won't be any gifts.
or visits from Santa. but...
We're having a special dinner
like last year. right?
Don't even think about it.
You said they no longer had
to be chained.
We're just testing!
Oliver. help me.
He's right. Salvador.
We have made giant steps these days.
We barely have food for ourselves.
You said it yourself.
They’ll be happy with a couple of rats.
Pig.
Hello to my beloved audience!
Tonight is a very special night.
That’s why I'm going to sing
my Christmas carols!
Christmas is here.
Time for merriment and cheer.
With mom and dad today.
we're going to celebrate.
Christmas is here.
Time for merriment and cheer.
With mom and dad today.
we're going to celebrate.
Christmas is here. everything is neat.
Finally. tonight my family is complete.
Finally. tonight my family is complete!
Thank you. beautiful crowd!
Thank you.
A little closer. Benja.
Smile. Oliver.
Ready?
Let me see.
Can I see?
I want to see it.
Look dad.
Look dad. dad. look at the photo.
The photo.
Look.
Look mom.
This is dad. this is Salvador.
This is Oliver. this is me.
This is you.
She does recognize us!
She recognizes herself!
She doesn't like it!
Oliver take the muzzles. quick!
Ah!
Benjamin. what are you doing?
I want to teach them to eat real food.
Put on your helmet. be careful.
Look. mommy.
It's soup. it's delicious.
Look mom. here comes the airplane.
Oliver. there's someone outside!
Take them downstairs.
fast run. run. run!
Run. run!
- Who else is in the house?
- Nobody!
- Who?
- My parents went out.
- What about those screams?
- We were...
- Hey. hey don't move.
We were in the middle of Christmas dinner.
Do you have water?
Give it to me.
Is there dessert? Chocolate?
A cigarette?
Fuck yes.
Who knew cigarettes expire?
All I have found are either dry or rancid.
But whatever.
Tobacco is tobacco.
Where did your parents go?
They went looking for food.
How long ago?
Why do you have an eye
with a different color?
Because I'm a witch.
I saw you in the woods.
sorry if I scared you.
I just wanted to see what you had.
I found the map in your backpack and came.
The radio got screwed because of the water.
Who are the people hanging outside?
They lived here before.
Who hung them?
- My dad did.
- Did he...?
No. they were like that
when we got here.
Take them down.
They attract too much attention.
Halloween is over.
These windows must also be covered.
The decoration of this place is... curious.
Have you seen a plane around here?
Or have you heard them?
They're Russian.
they have the Red Cross.
They fly around the world
dropping cold boxes with the cure.
Medicine?
A vaccine?
You see. I told you.
There’s a cure?
A serum. Hyperimmune Gamma Globulin.
It reverses the symptoms of the virus
and avoids contagion.
I don't believe a damn thing.
The world went to shit
because of a poorly tested vaccine.
How do they drop them?
With parachutes.
They had to find it sooner or later.
right?
The bad news is they
rarely fly over this area anymore.
The way I see it.
we have two options.
Option number one.
We stay in this house. with the garden.
with all this. but without the cure.
Option number two.
We go out looking for the cure.
risk ourselves to find the best.
"We" stay?
Any fire trumpets nearby?
We haven't come across them.
We've only seen their tracks.
I'm sorry but you can't stay.
The trumpets killed
everyone in my group.
What are the trumpets?
Those are real monsters?
Want to watch a movie?
How do you watch it?
Are you kidding me?
It works without electricity?
Can we watch a movie?
What other movies do you have?
Just that one.
One movie and one record.
You can't stay here.
If my parents come and see you.
they won't like it.
Listen. Santiago.
- Salvador.
- Salvador. nice to meet you. I'm Valeria.
You're not going to let me go right now.
right?
At night.
It's dangerous. It's cold. I'm tired.
It's been months since
I've talked to someone.
And years since I watched a movie.
Please.
If you call that a movie.
Yes!
Who's going to play it?
What were they smoking
when they made this movie?
I'm sorry. I can't go any longer.
Oliver. to your room. Take him!
Okay. let's go.
Good night.
I was enjoying it.
Thanks.
It's the coolest thing
anyone has done for me in a long time.
Since before all this started.
No one ever rode a bike so I could
watch a movie.
Not to mention someone with only one leg.
No offense.
What about that bike?
My dad made it. he was an engineer.
He was?
He is.
I helped him.
What about your mother?
She's a nurse.
An engineer and a nurse!
Damn! You and your
brothers really got lucky!
What happened to you?
I'm going to bed.
I'll get you some blankets.
No. wait. huh?
I want to take a bath.
May I?
Is that magazine good?
Can I borrow a shirt or what?
Thanks for heating the water.
It was delicious.
What do we have here?
You know I've never been with a virgin?
What?
I want to pay you
for what you've done for me.
Let me do it.
When was the last time you saw a girl?
Exactly.
I haven't had many opportunities. either.
Besides. it's easy and delicious.
Like wanking?
Much more.
I can stay with you.
We can talk to your parents.
We have to repopulate the world. right?
Two extra hands might be useful.
We're fine. we don't need your help.
Why?
Why don't you share with those of us
who are also trying to survive?
You don't know how things are
outside.
With the infected.
The trumpets.
Well.
Just for tonight.
Should I turn off the lights?
That was incredible.
Thanks.
I know you've had a very hard time
like everyone.
but you can't stay.
Forgive me.
Hold me until dawn.
Then you won't see me again.
Let's go.
Oliver. take your brother and lock up!
No! What's going to
happen to Salvador?
Oliver!
Take your brother and lock yourselves!
On the table!
Alcohol. quick!
Alcohol!
You are not gonna die!
I'm sorry honey!
I have to do it!
I'm sorry! Don't move. dammit!
Mom. am I going to die?
Don't move!
I'm gonna die!
You're not gonna die!
Calm down!
Look at me. look at me!
- Trust me. trust me.
- No dad. no!
Bite. bite hard.
- Bite hard!
- I'm sorry!
Bite hard!
I have to do it!
Hold on. hold on!
Hold him!
No. no!
Ah!
An infected? Do you keep an infected here?
You damn idiot. there are two kids here!
Ah!
No. no. no!
Get off! Get off!
Ah!
Leave her!
What was she doing there?
Where did she get the keys to go
down there?
What do we do with her body?
We can use it as fertilizer
for the garden.
It’s no good! It’s infected!
There’s only one thing to do.
Won't you say a few words or something?
What do you want me to say?
I let my guard down. like an idiot.
It won't happen to me
ever again.
They loved that girl's meat.
They've been eating
dogs and rats for a long time.
Look at them now.
We have to give them more.
Give them more?
Do you want them to be stronger?
We can barely control them.
No diet change. are we clear?
Are we sure about this?
This house is the highest point in miles.
What if the wrong people see it?
Imagine if it does work.
Imagine if the cure falls on us.
to be immune to the virus and above all...
To be able to cure mom and dad.
Mom.
Mom. eat this!
It’s meat!
Just as you like it.
Dad.
It's meat. it's going to rot!
Dad!
Eat!
So many years looking after them.
Looking after ourselves.
Hiding them. feeding them.
For what?
What’s the point of keeping them
in this suffering?
What's the point of educating them?
What fucking life is this?
Benjamin insists on the same.
he wants to give them Valeria's body.
What do you think?
I want them to be okay.
but I'm still afraid of them.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure he doesn't do anything
stupid.
Why don't you ever listen?
Don't you trust my decisions?
What will you do?
Don’t fucking ask.
Bugger off or cover your nose.
No!
“Once upon a time. there were
two children named Hansel and Gretel.
Who lived with their father. a lumberjack.
and their stepmother near a dense forest”.
“The family's situation was precarious.
They lived with scarcity and barely
had enough to eat”.
- Benja.
- You shut up!
"One night. the cruel stepmother"...
We have to give them something else.
I offered them everything
we have but they don't want it.
I told you we had to give them the body.
Maybe it's the best for them.
At least that way they'll stop suffering.
What are you talking about?
What else do you want to do?
Valeria's meat was good for them.
You want to kill to feed them?
We are not murderers.
You don't care about the cure
because you don't care about mom and dad!
You only care about your fucking rules!
You don't believe they are people!
They are not people. Benjamin!
People are those who are out there
in the real world.
if you kill them. you're a murderer.
We kill dogs.
It's not the same.
Don't be stupid.
Besides. tell me who is going to do it?
You. Benjamin?
You can't even kill a fly.
You. Oliver?
You can't even skin a fucking dead dog.
They are our parents!
You want them to die!
What I want is to save our family!
I'm not going to argue anymore.
You will not leave until the three of us
agree on what to do.
Let's vote!
Those who want to... hunt for... food
for mom and dad
raise your hand.
Those who want to let them die.
Do whatever the fuck you want.
I want to see who kills who.
The ground is too hard.
Why don't we just use Guillermina?
To kill someone with Guillermina
you need to be very close.
How much are we going to dig?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
That's a lot.
It has to be deep enough.
so it can't get out.
Then how do we get it out?
With a rope.
Who is going to tie it?
Between the two of us.
And how are we going to get out?
"One night. the cruel stepmother
suggested to the good lumberjack
who was suffering thinking
that his children were starving".
"We must abandon them in the forest".
"There's not enough food".
"Maybe someone will find them.
take pity and feed them".
"At first. the father was adamantly opposed
to the idea of abandoning
his children to the mercy of the forest".
Wake up you lazy bastards.
Are you ready to build an awesome trap?
That's how it has to look. Just add
some more leaves to cover the planks.
Any questions?
Hold this.
Here is a military checkpoint.
Where Benjamin and I saw clothes hanging.
All this is forest.
On your way back.
the sun has to be on your left.
Also behind you in the afternoon.
Without the radios
I can't help you at all.
If you get lost. you're on your own.
If you see the trumpets
or some other infected. run!
Understood?
That's how mom and dad would end
if we don't feed them.
What are we going to do?
Hurry up.
I think this is where Salvador pointed.
Come. let's set the camp.
Hey. let me look too.
Come. let's go.
Help!
Somebody help me. please!
It hurts a lot!
It hurts me!
Help me!
Help!
Someone help me please!
What are you doing here kid?
I got lost.
Who’s with you?
I'm alone.
Were you bitten?
Answer me! Were you bitten?
Ah!
Calm down.
I'm going to help you.
Stupid kids. what do you want?
Shit. what do you want?
You're going to kill me?
Huh?
You're going to shoot me like an infected?
Look me in the eyes. you bastard!
Kill me.
Are you scared?
Kill me!
Shoot here!
Shoot asshole. if you're going to kill me.
look me in the eye!
Look me in the eye!
You wanted to kill me. asshole?
Let me go!
Quick. Let's go.
Don't look back.
Congratulations.
You did it.
I'm proud of you.
But this is just the beginning.
- What is it?
- No idea.
Should we go out?
What if it's a plane?
Planes don't sound like that.
Go to your room.
I'll stay here watching.
I brought you water.
a guava. and a blanket.
Tomorrow we'll take a walk.
You and Benjamin sleep in the basement.
Hide. hide. fast!
Go away or I'll shoot!
I'm not here to steal or harm anyone.
I just want to hide.
Go away or I'll shoot!
Only the Almighty knows
when and where my life will end.
I'd rather die from a bullet
than getting caught.
Infected?
No. worse.
But it’s only children!
- Innocents!
- Hey. hey. hey!
Not one more step I said.
Who are they?
Trumpets.
Only if we help each other
can we fight them.
Quick!
Bring a hammer and nails.
We have to put this back.
Come on.
Those bastards will be here soon!
Do you know about the cure?
The sacred mantle to walk through
this hell without burning.
The salvation of the Chosen ones.
It is in the hands of the 144.000.
They say.
there are no more cures
for this entire region of the country.
Perhaps the entire world.
Those Russian planes.
Those God's angels fly through the air
carrying and dropping the real cure
for the cure that did not work.
The last ones have been dropped
from the sky.
The last one fell directly
into the hands of the 144.000.
The trumpets.
They are the ones looking for that
infected being
who may deserve to be saved.
When the entire world ends.
They are the last to remain.
The 7 tribes of the Chosen.
Only 144.000 people and not one more.
Are you with them?
Or are you left over?
Do you know the sacred scriptures?
The bible and those things?
- I know the ideology of the trumpets.
- The Book of the Law.
Didn't your parents instill in you
the study of the Holy Word?
They didn't read you the
psalms before going to bed?
What about the sacraments?
Did you take your first communion?
At least tell me you've been baptized.
What the hell do you care?
The 144.000...
walk the earth blowing their trumpet
just like the angels
who will announce the end of time.
“The first angel blew his trumpet.
there was hail and fire
mixed with blood that fell on the earth.
A third of the trees and grass
was burned”.
“Then the second angel played...
and a mountain caught fire.
It crashed into the ocean.
turning the waters to blood.
killing the fish and destroying the ships”.
“The third angel played and a star fell
into rivers and fountains.
The waters became bitter.
Many men died”.
“When the fourth angel played. the sun.
the moon and the stars were darkened.
There was no light either day...
or night”.
“Another angel flew and said...
Oh. woe to those who die on Earth
at the sound of the trumpets”.
“When the last man
who didn't belong to the 144.000 dies.
The chosen ones will be called
to take their place next to God”.
So. for the last time.
You heathen brats.
Have you been baptized or not?
Why do you keep
checking your watch?
Because it's time!
Trumpets!
Run to the basement!
You do not belong to the seven tribes!
You lost your chance at salvation.
You must die so the Father may come.
I'm sorry.
You can go out without me.
How many Enoc?
Three.
They are just children.
Children?
- But we agreed that all kids...
- Listen to me.
These impure creatures do not belong here.
They have not been baptized.
There's only one thing we can do.
Infected.
You go.
Tie it!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let me go. now!
It's your parents fault.
They did not instill in you
the fear of God.
Now. our ritual will sanctify your soul
and free you forever from this world.
No. no. no!
No!
Let him go!
Dad!
- No!
No!
Dad!
No. dad. no!
Oh. Almighty!
Oh. Merciful and Perfect!
Impeccable. Infinite Circle!
Bless our brotherhood.
Let us know that we do right.
You who from heaven sent us your blessing.
The last cure of the area.
Guide our hand in the sacrifice of those
who by breathing.
do not allow your will to be fulfilled.
No! Salvador! Get away from him!
- Let him go!
- Salvador!
Leave me!
Let him go!
No! Salvador!
Leave me. leave me!
Please let me go! Let me go!
No! Please!
Let him go!
No. no. no!
"Isaac broke the silence!
And said to his father Abraham."
Salvador!
Help. help me!
"We have wood and fire.
but we don't have
the lamb for the holocaust".
Let me go!
"God.
Please. no!
God will provide the lamb
Let him go!
For the holocaust!"
No!
Ah!
Salvador!
No!
Salvador.
No. no. no!
Salvador!
No! No! No!
Oliver!
Give it to me!
If you can take it from me. it's yours.
If not...
Get ready to reunite with your brother.
Only the one who brought me into the world
Can dispose of my soul.
- Leave me.
- Oliver!
Bite me all what you want. beast.
The blessed serum runs through my veins.
You bastard!
Mom! Mom!
Mom. we're going to help you.
Hold her!
No. no. no!
Let him go.
Benjamin. Benjamin!
I don't want to get infected!
I don't want to. I don't want to!
- You're not going to get infected!
- I don't want to!
You're not gonna get infected.
I promise you!
We´re going to find another cure.
We will go to the lake again.
You will sing another concert for us.
We will play in the woods again.
I promise you Benjamin.
I promise you. there must be another cure.
The little brother becomes the big brother.
and the big brother becomes the little one.
The father becomes the mother.
and the mother becomes the father.
The children become the parents
and the parents become the children.
But at the same time.
everything remains the same.
There are only two true
constants in the world:
Family and change.
Everything else doesn't matter.
For my brothers.
Jonathan and Eddy...
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org